<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<contents>
	<content contentID="banner" type="landing">
		<body><![CDATA[
 			<a href=""><img width="618px" height="330px" src="/media/images/banner/landingslider1.jpg"  alt="" title="#slide1" /></a> <a href=""><img width="618px" height="330px" src="/media/images/banner/landingslider2.jpg"  alt="" title="#slide2" /></a>
 		]]></body>
	</content>
	<content contentID="ideal" type="product">
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p>
			Showcasing a wide collection of perfect coffee makers, dinner sets, tea sets, kitchen accessories, stainless steel utensils, bar accessories, bed covers, cushions, rugs, bath mats, carpets, place mats, etc....
			</p>
			<h2>
			An Introduction
			</h2>
			<p>
			Here, at Home Ideal, a vast collection of kitchen accessories, bar accessories, home furnishing items, etc. are manufactured using latest manufacturing techniques. Quality maintenance is another positive aspect of this organization.
			</p>
			<p>
			Today this firm has been adjudged as the champion manufacturer, exporter and importer of coffee makers, dinner sets, tea sets, kitchen accessories, stainless steel utensils, bar accessories, bed covers, cushions, rugs, bath mats, carpets, place mats, etc. We cover the entire continent of Europe, America & South America under our export market whereas a part of Europe, China & South East Asian nations, falls under the canopy of our import market. 
			</p>
			<p>
			We process high grade steel for manufacturing variety of utensils in different shapes and volumes. Other products such as home furnishing items are made out of good quality fabrics. Bed sheets, cushions, curtains, etc. are available in attractive designs and exquisite embroideries.
			</p>
			<p>
			Our expertize enables us to develop products as per the specifications given by the clients. We work with a customer centric approach therefore quote price for products which is nominal and competitive. Further we are proud to announce that our product delivery mechanism is prompt and punctual. One can count on us for all types of high quality kitchenware and home furnishing items. 
			</p>
			<h2>
			Product Range
			</h2>
			<p>
			Home Ideal is a well recognized firm in the international markets because its products are used by the clients from all over the world. The company has an edge in this regard over its competitors. Every product manufactured by this organization is an icon of quality, long shelf life and advanced features. Our product range includes:
			</p>
			<p>
			Coffee makers
			Dinner sets
			Tea sets
			Kitchen accessories
			Stainless steel utensils
			Bar accessories
			Imported glassware
			Tumblers
			Vacuum flasks
			Home furnishing items: Bed covers, cushions, rugs, bath mats, carpets, place mats, etc.
			</p>
			<h2>
			Assured Quality
			</h2>
			<p>
			Our quality management system is such that even a minute flaw in a product is quickly detected and the corrective measures are immediately initiated. In this regard, the role played by our quality staff is appreciable and praise worthy.
			</p>
			Quality has been the first and foremost concern of our organization since our company's inception. We ensure supply of premium quality kitchen accessories, bar accessories and home furnishing items on the base of excellent quality control system.  
			<h2>  
			The Inside Story
			</h2>
			<p>
			Our manufacturing unit is segregated into three segments. One segment is meant for manufacturing high quality kitchen utensils and allied accessories. At the second segment, bar accessories are developed. The third segment is fully dedicated to manufacture all types of stylish and trendy home furnishing items.
			</p>
			We have installed latest machines and equipment to each segment for effective and flawless production of our products. Daksh Exim Solutions Pvt. Ltd. is well supported by its manpower. Some prominent personnel are engineers, designers, quality analysts, research staff, amongst others. With wide marketing network across the globe, we ensure timely delivery under any circumstances.  
			</p>	
   		]]>
		</body>
	</content>
	<content contentID="customer-serv" type="landing">
		<body><![CDATA[
 			<h3 class="ico ico2">24 x 7 Customer Support +91 9871997564</h3>
 			<p>Need help? or If you have any questions about any product or service that you purchased or buy from onshopp call immediately or email us. </p>
 			<span class="email">Email: info@Onshopp.com</span>  
 		]]></body>
	</content>
	<content contentID="free-shipping" type="landing">
		<body><![CDATA[
 			<h3 class="ico ico4">Free Shipping</h3>
			<p>Onshopp provides free delivery on all items for total order amount is Rs. 500/- or more.</p>
 		]]></body>
	</content>
	<content contentID="offers" type="landing">
		<body><![CDATA[
 			<h3 class="ico ico3">Promotional Offers </h3>
			<p>Onshopp have most attractive promotional offers and hot deals on electronic ,lifestyle,kitchen and gift items</p>
 		]]></body>
	</content>
	<content contentID="time-delivery" type="landing">
		<body><![CDATA[
 			<h3 class="ico ico1">Delivery On Time</h3>
				<p>Gurranted delivery! Onshopp deliver as earliest as possible within the time mention on item details box.</p>
 		]]></body>
	</content>
	<content contentID="cod" type="landing">
		<body><![CDATA[
 			<h3 class="ico">Check Cash/cheque on Delivery</h3>
				<p>
					You can pay Cash/cheque on Delivery . Unfortunately this service is available in delhi NCR only.				   
				</p> 
 			]]></body>
	</content>
	<content contentID="lowest-price" type="landing">
		<body><![CDATA[
 			<h3 class="ico">your price</h3>
				<p>
					if you are not satisfy with product price. you can bid your price with phone number or email.We assure you that we would try our best to meet your price. 
				</p> 
 			]]></body>
	</content>
	<content contentID="weekly-deal" type="landing">
		<body><![CDATA[
 			<h3 class="ico">weekly Deals</h3>
				<p>
					Product Title : 16PCSBAR SET is hottest product.Stock have been limited.  go & buy					  				   
				</p> 
									<div class="box">									
									<div class="tp_mg10 ac" style="position:relative;">															
																<a href="/onshopp/kitchenware-accessories/bar-accessories/S7354010_buy"><img src="/media/images/product/16PCSBAR%20SET.jpg" height="290px" width="290px"> </a>															
														<div class="product-info">															
															<h3>16PCSBAR SET</h3>	
															<div class="product-desc ac">																										
																<div class="product-price"><div style="width:50%;float:left;"><strike>INR 2999</strike></div><div style="width:50%;float:right;"><font color="red">INR 1900</font><br><font style="font-size:75%;" color="red">Save: 36% OFF</font></div></div>	
																		<div class="button-left">
																			<a href="/onshopp/kitchenware-accessories/bar-accessories/S7354010_buy">
																				<div class="href-button">
																					<span class="button1-box1"></span>
																					<span class="button1-box2a">Details</span>
																					<span class="button1-box3"></span>
																				</div>
																			</a>
																		</div>
																	<div class="clear"></div>																																																
															</div>
															
														</div>
														<div class="clear"></div>											
									</div>
								<div class="clear"></div>	
								<h2 class="blubg ac">Deals Of Week</h2>
							</div>
							<div class="clear"></div>
 			]]></body>
	</content>
</contents>